# **Keneil Jordan**

# **Computing Graduate**

Mobile: +447774550700

**LinkedIn:** <a href="https://www.linkedin.com/in/keneil-jordan">https://www.linkedin.com/in/keneil-jordan</a>

Email: keneiljordan@hotmail.co.uk

### **SUMMARY**

A recent computing graduate with commercial experience working in software development. I have gained 1 year of work experience under a commercial company as an apprentice during my gap year with exposure to a full agile software development cycle as a member of a team. This includes working on the front and backend of the web systems, conducting tasks such as integrating UI designs, testing and publishing to the live systems mainly using C#/ASP.NET, HTML, CSS, SQL and Umbraco. I am actively looking to learn and gain professional experience in software development while embracing the challenges ahead of me in future projects and endeavours.

#### **TECHNICAL SKILLS**

- C#
- .NET
- Object Orientated Programming
- Java
- PHP
- Agile / Scrum
- Umbraco
- Microsoft Office (Access/Excel, PP, Word)
- Bootstrap

- Adobe Illustrator/Photoshop
- HTML5, CSS, JavaScript
- Testing/Debugging
- MVC
- SQL Management Studio / MySQL
- NodeJS
- CMS/WordPress
- Android Studio

# **PREVIOUS EMPLOYMENT**

# **Apprentice Systems Developer, Enact Conveyancing**

September 2015 - September 2016

- Demonstrated strong teamworking skills which also helped to build communication with stakeholders when discussing project methodologies.
- Contributed to development of new implementations to the live ASP.NET to create a Model View Controller (MVC) web app.
- Offered support to clients with less technical knowledge to help solve complex problems.
- Time management was key to completing deadlines on time in order to have software fully evaluated before release.
- Acquired multiple skills in coding languages such as C#, HTML CSS, JavaScript, PHP and SQL whilst studying at Estio Training in Halifax.

#### Sales Assistant, Sports Direct

#### June 2018 – October 2019

- Being responsible for processing cash and card payments.
- Answering queries from customers.
- Working within established guidelines, particularly with brands.
- Keeping up to date with special promotions and putting up displays.
- Assisting shoppers to find the goods and products they are looking for.

#### **Crew Member, McDonalds**

October 2014 - July 2015

- Built customer experience and communication skills to provide an exceptional service.
- Acquired strong management skills in order to oversee busy tasks while aiding newer staff effectively during busy hours.
- Adapting and adhering to health standards were learnt from working in the kitchen.
- Teamwork and Respect ensure that the workflow is efficient and effective to help tackle the fast paced working environment.

#### **QUALIFICATIONS**

**Manchester Metropolitan University** 

**Sept 2016 – July 2020** 

BSc(Hons) Computing

1st Class

*Modules included:* Advanced Programming, Web design and development, Data engineering, Mobile applications development and Web based business systems.

**ESTIO Training** 

Sep 2015 – Sep 2016

Level 3 Diploma in ICT Competence

Level 3 Diploma in ICT Systems and Principles

Advanced Level Apprenticeship in IT, Software, Web & Telecoms Professionals

Modules Including: Software Testing, Website Software, Web Development, Object Oriented Computer Program Using C#, Data Modelling.

Leeds City College Sep 2013 – July 2015

Level 3 BTEC subsidiary diploma in IT: DM

City of Leeds High School Sep 2008 – July 2013

GCSE 5(Including Maths, English)

# **INTERESTS**

- Avid gamer and have developed a pure JavaScript game as part of my dissertation project whilst studying at university as well as a database system.
- Very much into art and Asian culture, occasionally draws and enjoy anime, science fiction and competitive eSports. I Also enjoy quality social time with friends and family whether it's at a pub, arcade or bowling alley.
- Personal development and growth are important to me so I prioritise fitness and work out at least 3 times a week.

**References Available on Request.**